Guide to the Portland Reporter Photographs Collection 1960-1964
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- People Files, 1960-1964; Series B
  - Ove--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 103/20)
  - Owe--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 103/21)
  - Owings, 1962 (Box-folder 103/22)
  - Ownbeys, 1964 (Box-folder 103/23)
  - Oya--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 103/24)
  - Pabst, 1961 (Box-folder 103/25)
  - Pac--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 103/26)
  - Pad--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 103/27)
  - Pae--, 1962 (Box-folder 103/28)
  - Pag--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 103/29)
  - Poh--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 103/30)
  - Pai--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 103/31)
  - Pal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 103/32)
  - Pam--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 103/33)
  - Pan--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 103/34)
  - Pao--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 103/35)
  - Pap--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 103/36)
  - Paque, 1960 (Box-folder 103/37)
  - Par--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 103/38)
  - Par--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 104/1)
  - Par--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 104/2)
  - Par--, 1962 (Box-folder 104/3)
  - Par--, 192-1963 (Box-folder 104/4)
  - Pas--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 104/5)
  - Pat--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 104/6-7)
  - Pau--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 104/8)
  - Pav--, 1963 (Box-folder 104/9)
  - Pawley, 1961 (Box-folder 104/10)
  - Paxson, 1961 (Box-folder 104/11)
  - Pay--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 104/12)
  - Paz--, 1963 (Box-folder 104/13)
  - Pea--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 104/14)
  - Pea--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 104/15)
  - Pec--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 104/16)
  - Ped--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 105/1)
  - Pee--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 105/2)
  - Pef--, 1963 (Box-folder 105/3)
  - Pel--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 105/4)
  - Pem--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 105/5)
  - Pen--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 105/6)
  - Pep--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 105/7)
  - Per--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 105/8)
  - Per--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 105/9)
  - Pes--, 1960 (Box-folder 105/10)
  - Pet--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 105/11-13)
  - Pey--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 105/14)
  - Pezoldt, 1964 (Box-folder 105/15)
  - Pfa--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 105/16)
  - Pfi--, undated; 1962 (Box-folder 105/17)
  - Pha--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 106/1)
  - Phe--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 106/2)
  - Phi--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 106/3)
  - Phi--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 106/4)
  - Pho--, 1963 (Box-folder 106/5)
  - Pia--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 106/6)
  - Pic--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 106/7)
  - Pid--, 1962 (Box-folder 106/8)
  - Pie--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 106/9)
  - Pig--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 106/10)
  - Pih--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 106/11)
  - Pik--, 1960 (Box-folder 106/12)
  - Pil--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 106/13)
  - Pin--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 106/14)
  - Pio--, 1960 (Box-folder 106/15)
  - Pip--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 106/16)
  - Pis--, 1961 (Box-folder 106/17)
  - Pit--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 106/18)
  - Pla--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 106/19)
  - Ple--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 107/1)
  - Pli--, 1962 (Box-folder 107/2)
  - Plo--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 107/3)
  - Plu--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 107/4)
  - Ply--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 107/5)
  - Pob--, 1963 (Box-folder 107/6)
  - Pochert, 1963 (Box-folder 107/7)
  - Poelwijk, 1960 (Box-folder 107/8)
  - Pof--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 107/9)
  - Poh--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 107/10)
  - Poi--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 107/11)
  - Pol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 107/12)
  - Pom--, 1962 (Box-folder 107/13)
  - Pon--, 1962 (Box-folder 107/14)
  - Poo--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 107/15)
  - Pop--, 1962 (Box-folder 107/16)
  - Por--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 107/17)
  - Pos--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 107/18)
  - Pot--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 107/19)
  - Pou--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 107/20)
  - Pov--, 1962 (Box-folder 107/21)
  - Pow--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 107/22)
  - Pow--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 107/23)
  - Pow--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 107/24)
  - Poy--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 107/25)
  - Poz--, 1960 (Box-folder 107/26)
  - Pra--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 107/27)
  - Pre--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 107/28)
  - Pri--, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 108/1)
  - Pri--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 108/2)
  - Puhl--, 1964 (Box-folder 108/3)
  - Ragouzardis, 1964 (Box-folder 108/4)
  - Rakocinski, undated (Box-folder 108/5)
  - Raistakka, 1964 (Box-folder 108/6)
  - Ramsey, 1964 (Box-folder 108/7)
  - Rayburn, Gene, undated (Box-folder 108/8)
  - Reynolds, 1964 (Box-folder 108/9)
  - Riggs, 1963 (Box-folder 108/10)
  - Roc--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 108/11-13)
  - Rod--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 108/14)
  - Roe--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 108/15)
  - Rof--, 1961 (Box-folder 108/16)
  - Rog--, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 108/17)
  - Roh--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 108/18)
  - Roi--, 1961 (Box-folder 108/19)
  - Rol--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 108/20)
  - Rom--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 109/1)
  - Ron--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 109/2)
  - Roo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 109/3)
  - Roosevelts, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 109/4-5)
  - Rop--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 109/6)
  - Ror--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 109/7)
  - Ros--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 109/8-10)
  - Rot--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 109/11)
  - Ruby, 1964 (Box-folder 109/12)
  - Ruether, 1964 (Box-folder 109/13)
  - Rus--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 109/14)
  - Rus--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 110/1)
  - Russell, Mrs. Douglas, 1962 (Box-folder 128/39)
  - Sale, 1964 (Box-folder 110/2)
  - Sarnoff, undated (Box-folder 110/3)
  - Schwartz, 1964 (Box-folder 110/4)
  - Sckavone, 1962 (Box-folder 110/5)
  - Sco--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 110/6)
  - Scs--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 110/7)
  - Scr--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 110/8)
  - Scu--, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 110/9)
  - Sea--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 110/10)
  - Seb--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 110/11)
  - Sechser, 1963 (Box-folder 110/12)
  - Sed--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 110/13)
  - See-, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 110/14)
  - Seg--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 110/15)
  - Sei--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 110/16)
  - Sel--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 110/17)
  - Sem--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 110/18)
  - Sen--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 110/19)
  - Sequeira, Lei, 1962 (Box-folder 110/20)
  - Ser--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 110/21)
  - Ses--, 1962 (Box-folder 110/22)
  - Set--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 110/23)
  - Seubert, 1961 (Box-folder 110/24)
  - Sev--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 110/25)
  - Sexson, 1960 (Box-folder 110/26)
  - Sey--, 1962 (Box-folder 110/27)
  - Seziol, 1961 (Box-folder 110/28)
  - Sha--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 111/1)
  - Sha--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 111/2)
  - 1961-1964 (Box-folder 111/3-4)
  - Shepard, Alan B., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 111/5-6)
  - Shi--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 111/7)
  - Shl--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 111/8)
  - Shmautz, 1960 (Box-folder 111/9)
  - Sho--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 111/10)
  - Sho--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 111/11)
  - Shr--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 112/1)
  - Shu--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112/2)
  - Shvernik, 1963 (Box-folder 112/3)
  - Sias, 1936 (Box-folder 112/4)
  - Sickles, 1964 (Box-folder 112/5)
  - Sidey, 1961 (Box-folder 112/6)
  - Sie--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112/7)
  - Sig--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 112/8)
  - Sikorsky, 1963 (Box-folder 112/9)
  - Sil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 112/10)
  - Sim--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 112/11-12)
  - Sin--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 112/13)
  - Sin--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 112/14)
  - Sin--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 112/15)
  - Sir--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 112/16)
  - Sis--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 112/17)
  - Sister, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112/18)
  - Sit--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 112/19)
  - Siu--, 1964 (Box-folder 112/20)
  - Siz--, 1961 (Box-folder 112/21)
  - Sjolund, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 112/22)
  - Ske--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 113/1)
  - Ski-, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 113/2)
  - Skjerbaek, 1963 (Box-folder 113/3)
  - Sko--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 113/4)
  - Skr--, 1963 (Box-folder 113/5)
  - Skulason, 1962 (Box-folder 113/6)
  - Sky--, 1962 (Box-folder 113/7)
  - Sla--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 113/8)
  - Sle--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 113/9)
  - Sli--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 113/10)
  - Slo--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 113/11)
  - Sma--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 113/12)
  - Sme--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 113/13)
  - Smi--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 113/14)
  - Smi--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 113/15)
  - Smi--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 113/16)
  - Smi--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 113/17)
  - Smi--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 113/18)
  - Smi--, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 113/19)
  - Smi--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 113/20)
  - Smi--, 1964 (Box-folder 113/21)
  - Smo--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 114/1)
  - Smu--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 114/2)
  - Smy--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 114/3)
  - Sna--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 114/4)
  - Sne--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 114/5)
  - Sni--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 114/6)
  - Sno--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 114/7)
  - Sny--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 114/8)
  - Sobels, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 114/9)
  - Soderberg, 1963 (Box-folder 114/10)
  - Soe--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 114/11)
  - Sohn, 1963 (Box-folder 114/12)
  - Soikkele, 1962 (Box-folder 114/13)
  - Sokolov, 1964 (Box-folder 114/14)
  - Sol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 114/15)
  - Som--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 114/16)
  - Son--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 114/17)
  - Soo--, 1962 (Box-folder 114/18)
  - Sor--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 114/19)
  - Sosa-Rodriguez, 1963 (Box-folder 114/20)
  - Sot--, 1961 (Box-folder 114/21)
  - Sou--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 114/22)
  - Sow--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 114/23)
  - Spa--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 114/24)
  - Spe--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 114/25)
  - Spi--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 114/26)
  - Spl--, 1964 (Box-folder 114/27)
  - Spo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 114/28)
  - Spr--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 114/29)
  - Spu--, 1963 (Box-folder 114/30)
  - Spyropoulus, 1962 (Box-folder 114/31)
  - Squier, 1963 (Box-folder 114/32)
  - Sta--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 115/1)
  - Sta--, 1961 (Box-folder 115/2)
  - Sta--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 115/3)
  - Sta--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 115/4)
  - Sta--, 1963 (Box-folder 115/5)
  - Sta--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 115/6)
  - Stageberg, Sandra, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 115/7)
  - Ste--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 115/8)
  - Ste--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 115/9)
  - Ste--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 116/1)
  - Ste--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 116/2)
  - Ste--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 116/3-4)
  - Ste--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 116/5)
  - Ste--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 116/6)
  - St. Martin, 1960 (Box-folder 116/7)
  - Stockwell, undated (Box-folder 116/8)
  - Str--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 116/9)
  - Sukarno, 1964 (Box-folder 116/10)
  - Sutton, 1964 (Box-folder 116/11)
  - Swenson, 1964 (Box-folder 116/12)
  - Taylor, 1964 (Box-folder 116/13)
  - Thao, 1964 (Box-folder 116/14)
  - Tho--, 1964 (Box-folder 116/15)
  - Thurmond, 1964 (Box-folder 116/16)
  - Tibbets, 1964 (Box-folder 116/17)
  - Tolan, 1964 (Box-folder 116/18)
  - Tucker, 1964 (Box-folder 116/19)
  - U-Pe, 1961 (Box-folder 117/1)
  - Usher, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 117/2)
  - Ustinov, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 117/3)
  - Utter, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 117/4)
  - Utzinger, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 117/5)
  - Uvoda, 1962 (Box-folder 117/6)
  - Uyesugi, 1962 (Box-folder 117/7)
  - Uyguanco, 1964 (Box-folder 117/8)
  - Vadset, 1962 (Box-folder 117/9)
  - Vail, 191; 1963 (Box-folder 117/10)
  - Val--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 117/11)
  - Van--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 117/12)
  - Van--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 117/13)
  - Van--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 117/14)
  - Van--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 117/15)
  - Vanderbilt, Bert, 1964 (Box-folder 128/40)
  - Vas--, 1962 (Box-folder 117/16)
  - Vau--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 117/17)
  - Vawter, 1964 (Box-folder 117/18)
  - Veazie, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 117/19)
  - Veggeberg, 1962 (Box-folder 117/20)
  - Veit, 1961 (Box-folder 117/21)
  - Vel--, 1962 (Box-folder 117/22)
  - Ven--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 117/23)
  - Ver--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 117/24)
  - Ves--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 117/25)
  - Vet--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 117/26)
  - Veveiros, 1960 (Box-folder 117/27)
  - Vial, 1964 (Box-folder 117/28)
  - Vic--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 117/29)
  - Vie--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 117/30)
  - Vie--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 117/31)
  - Vig--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 117/32)
  - Vik--, 1961 (Box-folder 117/33)
  - Vil--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 117/34)
  - Vin--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 117/35)
  - Viola, 1961 (Box-folder 117/36)
  - Virdon, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 117/37)
  - Visse, 1964 (Box-folder 117/38)
  - Vitale, 1961 (Box-folder 117/39)
  - Vla--, 1963 (Box-folder 117/40)
  - Voe--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 117/41)
  - Vogelpohl, 1964 (Box-folder 117/42)
  - Vol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 118/1)
  - Von-B--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 118/2)
  - Von-E--, 1961 (Box-folder 118/3)
  - Von-G--, 1962 (Box-folder 118/4)
  - Von-H--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 118/5)
  - Von-K--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 118/6)
  - Von-S--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 118/7)
  - Voorhies, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 118/8)
  - Vor--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 118/9)
  - Vos--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 118/10)
  - Votava, 1962 (Box-folder 118/11)
  - Vranizan, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 118/12)
  - Vukovich, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 118/13)
  - Waack, 1964 (Box-folder 118/14)
  - Wac--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 118/15)
  - Wad--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 118/16)
  - Wag--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 118/17)
  - Wah--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 118/18)
  - Wai--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 118/19)
  - Wak--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 118/20)
  - Wal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 118/21)
  - Wal--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 118/22)
  - Wal--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 118/23)
  - Wal--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 118/24)
  - Wal--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 118/25)
  - Wal--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 119/1)
  - Wal--, 1964 (Box-folder 119/2)
  - Wam--, 1963 (Box-folder 119/3)
  - Wan--, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 119/4)
  - War--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 119/5)
  - War--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 119/6)
  - War--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 119/7)
  - Was--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 119/8)
  - Wat--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 119/9)
  - Wat--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 119/10)
  - Wau--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 119/11)
  - Waverly, 1962 (Box-folder 119/12)
  - Waweru, 1963 (Box-folder 119/13)
  - Way--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 119/14)
  - Wea--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 119/15)
  - Web--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 120/1)
  - Wec--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 120/2)
  - Wed--, 1961-1062; 1964 (Box-folder 120/3)
  - Wee--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 120/4)
  - Weg--, 1961; 1064 (Box-folder 120/5)
  - Wehage, 1962 (Box-folder 120/6)
  - Wei--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 120/7)
  - Wei--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 120/8)
  - Wel--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 120/9)
  - Wel--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 120/10)
  - Wemhoener, 1962 (Box-folder 120/11)
  - Wen--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 120/12)
  - Wer--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 120/13)
  - Wes--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 120/14)
  - Wes--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 120/15)
  - Wet--, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 120/16)
  - Wexler, 1960 (Box-folder 120/17)
  - Wey--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 120/18)
  - Wha--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 121/1)
  - Whe--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 121/2)
  - Whi--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 121/3)
  - Whi--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 121/4)
  - Whi--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 121/5)
  - Wible, 1961 (Box-folder 121/6)
  - Wic--, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 121/7)
  - Wid--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 121/8)
  - Wie--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 121/9)
  - Wig--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 121/10)
  - Wik--, 1962 (Box-folder 121/11)
  - Wil--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 121/12)
  - Wil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 121/13-14)
  - Wil--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 122/1)
  - Wil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 122/2-3)
  - Wil--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 122/4)
  - Wil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 122/5-6)
  - Wim--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 122/7)
  - Win--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 122/8-9)
  - Wir--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 122/10)
  - Wis--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 123/1)
  - Wit--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123/2)
  - Wobig, 1962 (Box-folder 123/3)
  - Woerndle, 1961 (Box-folder 123/4)
  - Wohlers, 1963 (Box-folder 123/5)
  - Wol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123/6)
  - Wom--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 123/7)
  - Won--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 123/8)
  - Woo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123/9-11)
  - Wor--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 123/12)
  - Wreath, 1964 (Box-folder 123/13)
  - Wri--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123/14)
  - Wri--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 123/15)
  - Wroth, 1964 (Box-folder 123/16)
  - Wu--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 123/17)
  - Wuitschick, 1964 (Box-folder 123/18)
  - Wul--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 123/19)
  - Wusz, 1962 (Box-folder 123/20)
  - Wya--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123/21)
  - Wyckoff, 1962 (Box-folder 124/1)
  - Wyl--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 124/2)
  - Wym--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 124/3)
  - Wyn--, 1960-1062 (Box-folder 124/4)
  - Wys--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 124/5)
  - Yad--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 124/6)
  - Yager, 1964 (Box-folder 124/7)
  - Yak--, 1964 (Box-folder 124/8)
  - Yam--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 124/9)
  - Yan--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 124/10)
  - Yar--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 124/11)
  - Yates, 1962 (Box-folder 124/12)
  - Yav--, 1963 (Box-folder 124/13)
  - Yaw--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 124/14)
  - Yea--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 124/15)
  - Yee--, 1962 (Box-folder 124/16)
  - Yei--, 1962 (Box-folder 124/17)
  - Yelovich, 1962 (Box-folder 124/18)
  - Yeomans, 1961 (Box-folder 124/19)
  - Yer--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 124/20)
  - Yez--, 1960 (Box-folder 124/21)
  - Yggeseth, 1960 (Box-folder 124/22)
  - Yin--, 1961 (Box-folder 124/23)
  - Yor--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 124/24)
  - Yos--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 124/25)
  - Yau--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 124/26)
  - You--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 124/27-28)
  - Ytu--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 124/29)
  - Yu--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 124/30)
  - Yun--, 1963 (Box-folder 124/31)
  - Yurkus, 1962 (Box-folder 125/1)
  - Yutze, 1964 (Box-folder 125/2)
  - Zabaleta, 1964 (Box-folder 125/3)
  - Zachary, 1963 (Box-folder 125/4)
  - Zaffina, 1961 (Box-folder 125/5)
  - Zah--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/6)
  - Zaik, 1963 (Box-folder 125/7)
  - Zak--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 125/8)
  - Zal--, 1962 (Box-folder 125/9)
  - Zan--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 125/10)
  - Zarones, 1963 (Box-folder 125/11)
  - Zav--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 125/12)
  - Zaz--, 1962 (Box-folder 125/13)
  - Zeal, 1963 (Box-folder 125/14)
  - Zech, 1964 (Box-folder 125/15)
  - Zed--, 1961 (Box-folder 125/16)
  - Zeh--, 1964 (Box-folder 125/17)
  - Zeigler, 1962 (Box-folder 125/18)
  - Zel--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 125/19)
  - Zem--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 125/20)
  - Zen--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 125/21)
  - Zer--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 125/22)
  - Zesiger, 1963 (Box-folder 125/23)
  - Zetterling, 1962 (Box-folder 125/24)
  - Zezak, 1961 (Box-folder 125/25)
  - Zeck, 1960 (Box-folder 125/26)
  - Zidell, 1964 (Box-folder 125/27)
  - Zie--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 125/28)
  - Zika, 1961 (Box-folder 125/29)
  - Zil--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 125/30)
  - Zim--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/31)
  - Zin--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 125/32)
  - Zio--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/33)
  - Zip--, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/34)
  - Ziska, 1961 (Box-folder 125/35)
  - Zol--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/36)
  - Zom, 1960 (Box-folder 125/37)
  - Zonn, 1962 (Box-folder 125/38)
  - Zor--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 125/39)
  - Zschoche, 1962 (Box-folder 125/40)
  - Zub--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 125/41)
  - Zuc--, 1961 (Box-folder 125/42)
  - Zuercher, 1962 (Box-folder 125/43)
  - Zukor, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/44)
  - Zumas, 1960 (Box-folder 125/45)
  - Zur--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 125/46)
  - Zwa--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 125/47)
  - Zwe--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 125/48)
  - Zwick, 1961 (Box-folder 125/49)
  - Zygulski, 1963 (Box-folder 125/50)
  - Uncatergorized, 1964 (Box-folder 125/51)
- Cartoons and Other Photomechanical Materials, 1960-1964; Series C
  The art work and printed materials in this series are arranged by size, and then alphabetically by subject.
  - Automobile racing drawing, 1963 (Box-folder 128/41)
  - Automobile racing drawing, 1963 (Box-folder Oversize B1/14)
  - Benjamin Franklin Savings and Loan, 1962 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
  - Berlands Shoes building, 1962 (Box-folder 128/42)
  - Building at 1541 SW Market Street, Portland (drawing), 196 (Box-folder 128/42)
  - Cartoon by Don Bevan (photographic copy), undated (Box-folder 126/1)
  - Cartoons by Bill Mauldin
    - Pink forms of Mauldin cartoons for creating newspaper plates, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 126/2)
    - Half-tone prints of Mauldin cartoons, 1960; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 126/3-11)
  - Cartoon by Walt Miller (halftone), undated (Box-folder 126/12)
  - Cartoon by Mindolovich(orginal art), undated (Box-folder 126/13)
  - Highway--Portland Stadium Freeway, 1962 (Box-folder Oversize B1/17)
  - Journal Building (newspaper supplement), circa 1945 (Box-folder Oversize B1/15)
  - Klamath Indian Reservation--Willamette Meridian, undated (Box-folder Oversize B1/16)
  - Rose Festival, 1964 (Box-folder Oversize B/3)
  - Streets--33rd Avenue, 1962 (Box-folder Oversize B1/18)
  - Urban renewal--South Auditorium, undated (Box-folder Oversize B1/14)